{
  "module1": {
    "number": 1,
    "name": "Day 1 - Web3",
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What is Web3?",
        "answers": [
          "Centralized internet that a few organizations control",
          "Decentralized internet",
          "An online network that can be easily hacked or manipulated",
          "Internet with unicorns"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Decentralized internet"
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "What is a big limitation of Web3?",
        "answers": [
          "Scalability - transactions can be quite slow",
          "Centralization - only a few people control it",
          "Costs - transactions are free",
          "Responsiveness - everything is done instantly"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Scalability - transactions can be quite slow"
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "Pick an example that describes Web3",
        "answers": [
          "Payment services may decide to not allow payments for certain types of work",
          "Servers for gig-economy apps could go down and affect worker income",
          "Payment apps require no personal data and can't prevent payments",
          "Facebook can censor and delete any account"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Payment apps require no personal data and can't prevent payments"
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What’s the problem with ownership of value in Web2?",
        "answers": [
          "None, we own everything on Web2",
          "Companies steal our data and use it as they please",
          "Early investors share profits with late investors",
          "Companies never experience data breaches"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Companies steal our data and use it as they please"
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of decentralization?",
        "answers": [
          "More transparency",
          "Less wealth concentration at the top",
          "Slower transactions",
          "Giving the web back to the people"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "More transparency"
      }
    ]
  },
  "module2": {
    "number": 2,
    "name": "Day 2 - Blockchain",
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What is a node?",
        "answers": [
          "A type of cryptocurrency",
          "A blockchain",
          "An exchange",
          "A computer on a blockchain network"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A computer on a blockchain network"
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "Who created Bitcoin?",
        "answers": [
          "Satoshi Nakamoto",
          "Samsung",
          "Apple",
          "China"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Satoshi Nakamoto"
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "What is a blockchain?",
        "answers": [
          "An exchange",
          "A centralized ledger",
          "A distributed ledger on a peer to peer network",
          "A type of payment"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A distributed ledger on a peer to peer network"
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What is a genesis block?",
        "answers": [
          "The last block of a blockchain",
          "The current block of a blockchain",
          "The first block of a blockchain",
          "The famous block that changed blockchain"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The first block of a blockchain"
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "True or False: Blockchain is the same as Bitcoin.",
        "answers": [
          "True",
          "False"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "False"
      }
    ]
  },
  "module3": {
    "number": 3,
    "name": "Day 3 - Blockchain Explorer",
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What is a blockchain explorer?",
        "answers": [
          "A server that handles transactions",
          "A software that is connected to nodes and draws data from the blockchain",
          "A physical place where you can see all blocks",
          "A substitute for a blockchain"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A software that is connected to nodes and draws data from the blockchain"
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "A transaction on the blockchain will stay there forever",
        "answers": [
          "True",
          "False"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "What is a miner?",
        "answers": [
          "A type of blockchain",
          "An algorithm that predicts the next part of the chain",
          "A person doing calculations to verify a transaction",
          "Computers that verify and validate blockchain transactions"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Computers that verify and validate blockchain transactions"
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "When a record is on the blockchain, who can access it?",
        "answers": [
          "Multiple people simultaneously",
          "One person at a time",
          "Only people involved in the transaction"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Multiple people simultaneously"
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Once records are submitted on the blockchain, can they be altered?",
        "answers": [
          "Yes, the parties can go back and alter it",
          "Yes, but only within a certain time frame",
          "No, they cannot be altered"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "No, they cannot be altered"
      }
    ]
  },
  "module4": {
    "number": 4,
    "name": "Day 4 - Wallet",
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "Where do you store your cryptocurrency?",
        "answers": [
          "Bank account",
          "In my pocket",
          "Wallet",
          "CD player"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Wallet"
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "Where is the LEAST SAFE place to store your cryptocurrency?",
        "answers": [
          "On an exchange",
          "In your pocket",
          "In a hot wallet",
          "In a cold wallet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "On an exchange"
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "Where can you buy cryptocurrency?",
        "answers": [
          "Private transaction",
          "An exchange",
          "A Bitcoin ATM",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What is a private key?",
        "answers": [
          "A key on a keychain",
          "A key you hide under your bed",
          "A key not to be given to the public",
          "A key that you can use to hack someone’s car"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A key not to be given to the public"
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "What is a public key?",
        "answers": [
          "A key that’s publicly accessible",
          "A key that is only for you",
          "A key that opens a secret door",
          "A key that grants you access to someone’s account"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "A key that’s publicly accessible"
      }
    ]
  },
  "module5": {
    "number": 5,
    "name": "Day 5 - Hashing",
    "questions": [
      {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What does P2P stand for?",
        "answers": [
          "Password to Password",
          "Peer to Peer",
          "Product to Product",
          "Private key to Public key"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Peer to Peer"
      },
      {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "Asymmetric encryption uses",
        "answers": [
          "Public keys only",
          "Private keys only",
          "Public and Private keys",
          "Proof of Stake"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Public and Private keys"
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "What is a hash function?",
        "answers": [
          "A fork",
          "UTXO",
          "Takes an input of any length and returns a fixed-length string",
          "Gas"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Takes an input of any length and returns a fixed-length string"
      },
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What does a block in a blockchain consist of?",
        "answers": [
          "Transaction Data",
          "Hash point",
          "Timestamp",
          "All of these above"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "All of these above"
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "Cryptographic Hash Function transforms an arbitrary length of a fixed length string that act more or less as a Fingerprint of the document",
        "answers": [
          "Yes",
          "No"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Yes"
      }
    ]
  }
}
